

12 3 Main Street, Tampa,Florida,53609 j.jackson@youremail.com (123) 456-7890 Technically skilled and highly professional secretary with a business administration degree from the Florida Institute of Technology. Exceptional computer skills, including MS Office, Outlook Mail, CRM systems, and client booking systems. Aptitude for customer service, communication in-person and over the phone, problem-solving, and administration. Also has 2 years of industry secretarial experience, including working for two well-established accountancy firms. Dedicated to business success and improving working efficiency.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SECRETARY

Fitcher and Company Pampa CPA Firm Pampa, FI January 2020-February 2021

- Responsible for filing and scanning client's legal documents
- Scheduled client travel arrangements, meetings, and interviews
- Managed and updated all calendars and diaries for managerial staff
- Answered incoming emails and telephone calls
- Organized and filed all office paperwork and documents

SECRETARY

Walter S Sanders & Associates, Tampa, FL I July 2018 - January 2020

- Implement effective company policies to ensure that all practices comply with Labor and employment regulations
- Increased employee retention rates by managing workplace satisfaction to an over 90% success rate by creating and maintaining a positive work environment
- Develop targeted outreach practices to increase minority recruitment and ensure compliance with affirmative action policies
- Monitor scheduled in and out times as well as employee breaks to ensure that proper employment laws are met

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN
BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

Florida Institute Of Technology Melbourne, FL | August 2015 -July 2018

KEY SKILLS

- IT proficiency, including Microsoft Office (data sorting, validation, and filters)
- Knowledge of CRM and client booking systems
- Office management
- Administration
- Diary management
- Knowledge of CRM and client booking systems
- Excellent communication skills

CERTIFICATIONS

 Certified Administrative Professional by The International Association of Administrative Professionals, July 2018